[
    {
        "question": "What are natural numbers?",
        "answer": "natural numbers.md",
        "correct_attempts": 2,
        "total_attempts": 2,
        "unique_id": "math0001"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a numerator?",
        "answer": "The numerator is the top number in a fraction. It represents the number of parts you have out of the total number of parts.",
        "correct_attempts": 4,
        "total_attempts": 4,
        "unique_id": "math0002"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a denominator?",
        "answer": "The denominator is the bottom number in a fraction. It represents the total number of parts in the whole.",
        "correct_attempts": 3,
        "total_attempts": 3,
        "unique_id": "math0003"
    },
    {
        "question": "Solve for x:\n\n6055 + 2727 = x",
        "answer": "8782",
        "correct_attempts": 6,
        "total_attempts": 9,
        "unique_id": "math0004"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please write the following number as a rational number:\n\n5749",
        "answer": "5749\n---\n  1",
        "correct_attempts": 7,
        "total_attempts": 7,
        "unique_id": "math0005"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please write the following number as either a terminating or repeating decimal:\n\n9 \n --- \n 31",
        "answer": "repeating",
        "correct_attempts": 4,
        "total_attempts": 4,
        "unique_id": "math0006"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are whole numbers",
        "answer": "whole numbers.md",
        "correct_attempts": 2,
        "total_attempts": 2,
        "unique_id": "math0007"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are integers?",
        "answer": "integers.md",
        "correct_attempts": 2,
        "total_attempts": 2,
        "unique_id": "math0008"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are irrational numbers? Provide an example of an irrational number.",
        "answer": "Irrational numbers.md",
        "correct_attempts": 2,
        "total_attempts": 2,
        "unique_id": "math0009"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the order of operations?",
        "answer": "order of operations.md",
        "correct_attempts": 1,
        "total_attempts": 1,
        "unique_id": "math0010"
    },
    {
        "question": "Solve for x:\n\n2 x 2 = x",
        "answer": "4",
        "correct_attempts": 2,
        "total_attempts": 2,
        "unique_id": "math0011"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the commutative property of addition?",
        "answer": "commutative property of addition.md",
        "correct_attempts": 1,
        "total_attempts": 1,
        "unique_id": "math0012"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the commutative property of multiplication?",
        "answer": "commutative property of multiplication.md",
        "correct_attempts": 1,
        "total_attempts": 1,
        "unique_id": "math0013"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the associative property of multiplication?",
        "answer": "associative property of multiplication.md",
        "correct_attempts": 3,
        "total_attempts": 4,
        "unique_id": "math0014"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the distributive property?",
        "answer": "distributive property.md",
        "correct_attempts": 3,
        "total_attempts": 4,
        "unique_id": "math0015"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the identity property of addition?",
        "answer": "identity property of addition.md",
        "correct_attempts": 1,
        "total_attempts": 1,
        "unique_id": "math0016"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the identity property of multiplication?",
        "answer": "identity property of multiplication.md",
        "correct_attempts": 3,
        "total_attempts": 4,
        "unique_id": "math0017"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the inverse property of addition?",
        "answer": "inverse property of addition.md",
        "correct_attempts": 1,
        "total_attempts": 1,
        "unique_id": "math0018"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the inverse property of multiplication?",
        "answer": "inverse property of multiplication.md",
        "correct_attempts": 1,
        "total_attempts": 1,
        "unique_id": "math0019"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Mathematics, what is a constant?",
        "answer": "a constant is a value that does not change",
        "correct_attempts": 1,
        "total_attempts": 1,
        "unique_id": "math0020"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Mathematics, what is a variable?",
        "answer": "a variable is a symbol for a number we don't know yet. It is usually a letter like x or y. It a variable because it does not change",
        "correct_attempts": 1,
        "total_attempts": 1,
        "unique_id": "math0021"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Mathemetics, what is an equation?",
        "answer": "an equation says that two things are equal. It will have an equals sign = like this: 7 + 2 = 10 - 1",
        "correct_attempts": 1,
        "total_attempts": 1,
        "unique_id": "math0022"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Mathematics, what is a formula?",
        "answer": "a formula is a special type of equation that shows the relationship between different variables",
        "correct_attempts": 2,
        "total_attempts": 3,
        "unique_id": "math0023"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the Quadratic Formula?",
        "answer": "The quadractic formula is as follows: x = -b +/- sqrt(b^2 - 4ac) / 2a",
        "correct_attempts": 0,
        "total_attempts": 2,
        "unique_id": "math0024"
    },
    {
        "question": "Why is the Quadratic Formula important?",
        "answer": "The quadratic formula is important because it allows us to solve for the roots of a quadratic equation",
        "correct_attempts": 1,
        "total_attempts": 3,
        "unique_id": "math0025"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a quadratic equation?",
        "answer": "A quadratic equation is an equation of the form ax^2 + bx + c = 0, where a, b, and c are constants and a is not equal to 0",
        "correct_attempts": 1,
        "total_attempts": 3,
        "unique_id": "math0026"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what context do we use a quadratic equation?",
        "answer": "We use quadratic equations to model real world situations such as the trajectory of a ball thrown into the air",
        "correct_attempts": 1,
        "total_attempts": 2,
        "unique_id": "math0027"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are special product formulas?",
        "answer": "Special product formulas are formulas that allow us to quickly multiply certain types of polynomials",
        "correct_attempts": 1,
        "total_attempts": 1,
        "unique_id": "math0028"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the special product formulas?",
        "answer": "The special product formulas are as follows:\n\n(a + b)^2 = a^2 + 2ab + b^2\n\n(a - b)^2 = a^2 - 2ab + b^2\n\n(a + b)(a - b) = a^2 - b^2",
        "correct_attempts": 2,
        "total_attempts": 3,
        "unique_id": "math0029"
    }
]